Bhawna Agarwal

Product Designer with 5 years of formal design education, and 4+ years of experience designing and shipping well-crafted, high-impact experiences in the industry. I specialize in applying product thinking to break down complex problems and craft helpful experiences.

INDUSTRY EXPERIENCE

Product Designer, Wish

May-August 2020 (Intern), January 2021-Present (Full-time) | San Francisco

- Leading design for Wish Local pickup programs. Crafted and shipped several core app experiences in a fast-paced, collaborative environment making the user experience significantly better.
- Strategized and designed the end-to-end inventory management experience in the app from scratch. The design, and my design process was appreciated by stakeholders since it also helped them think about the Wish Local user journeys in new and more holistic ways.
- Demonstrated initiative by contributing to Wish's design system, and leading design for search filters for the Wish shopping app

UX Designer, Microsoft

April 2018-July 2019, Full-time | Hyderabad, India

- Sole designer for Microsoft's Azure Backup product (Enterprise software)
- Collaborated with 10+ product managers over multiple projects to deliver experiences for the Azure Backup service
- Owned the design, and delivered end-to-end experiences for Backup Center in close collaboration with PMs, Engineers, and the Azure UX team

UX Designer, Postman API Platform

June 2016-December 2017, Full-time | Bangalore, India

- Joined as the 21st employee, and reported to the CEO
- Applied extensive product thinking to envision, craft, and ship 6+ core
 projects within one year working as the sole designer. These experiences are
 providing productivity gains to 15 million+ users.
- Wore multiple hats provided customer support, and wrote product copy and feature marketing blog posts
- Was appreciated by the team for my ability to break down complex problems and conceptualize innovative solutions

Earlier experiences

- UX Designer, Housing.com, Full-time | June-December 2015
- UX Design Intern, HCII, Carnegie Mellon University | May-July 2014
- UX Design Intern, Robert Bosch | May–July 2013

EDUCATION

University of Michigan, Ann Arbor

Masters in Information

IIT Guwahati, India

Bachelor of Design with Minor in Computer Science

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Publications in ACM digital library as first author
- First position in OzCHI 2014 –
 International student design challenge
- · S.N. Bose Scholar

SKILLS

UX Research	Software
and Design	Figma
Contexual Inquiry	Sketch
User Interviews	Principle
Persona Building	Invision
Writing Job Stories	Photoshop
Info. Architecture	Illustrator
Heuristic Evaluation	InDesign
Usability Testing	Tableau
Wireframing	
Mobile Design	Coding
Visual/UI Design	HTML/ CSS
Prototyping	Javascript
UX Writing	jQuery
Storytelling	Python

PORTFOLIO

bhawna2109.github.io/